Guide to the International Brotherhood of Teamsters Local 544 records, 1930-2013 IBT0051
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Company Records, Series 3; 0 Linear Feet
  - Correspondence, handbooks, policy information, Series 3 Subseries 1
    - United Van Bus Delivery [5/7], 1980-1985; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - United Van Bus Delivery [6/7], 1981-1990; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - United Van Bus Delivery [7/7], 1984-1985; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - United Van Bus Delivery (Dahl and Curry), 1979-1980; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - United Van Bus Delivery, Marathon Division [1/2], 1982-1984; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - United Van Bus Delivery, Marathon Division [2/2], 1984-1988; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - Valley Memorial Hospital, 1987; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Valley News, 1990; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - Van Den Bergh Foods Company, 1987-1998; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - Van Ort, 1966; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - Van Voorst Trucking, Incorporated, 1979-1989; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 100, Folder 8)
    - Volk Transfer, 1971-1980; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 100, Folder 9)
    - Wallner Construction Company, 1977-1990; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 100, Folder 10)
    - Ward Transfer, Incorporated, 1975-1976; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 100, Folder 11)
    - Waymouth Farms, 1984; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 100, Folder 12)
    - Whirl-Air-Flow Equipment and Supply Company, Incorporated, 1977; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 100, Folder 13)
    - Wholesale Produce Supply Company, 1983; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - Winona Van Norman Division of Hein-Werner, 1986; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - Wintz Transportation Company, 1981-1987; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - Wis-Pak, Incorporated, 1989; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - Wisconsin Color Press, Incorporated, 1999; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - World Wide, Incorporated, 1978-1982; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Worthington Redi Mix, 1966-1979; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - Worthington Regional Hospital [1/2], 1979-1994; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - Worthington Regional Hospital [2/2], 1995-1999; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - Yellow Freight Systems, Incorporated, 1983-1990; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - Employee records, Series 3 Subseries 2
    - A.B.F. Freight System, 1990; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - A.B.I Machinery Movers, 1988; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - A.I.M. Drivers, Incorporated, 1983-1985; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - A.N.R. Freight System, Incorporated, 1985-1990; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - Abraham Transfer, 1971-1980; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - Ace Lines, Incorporated, 1975-1980; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - Acme Transfer and Storage Company, 1976; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - Advanced United Expressways, Incorporated [1/2], 1974-1979; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 103, Folder 8)
    - Advanced United Expressways, Incorporated [2/2], 1980-1986; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 103, Folder 9)
    - Ahmann Transfer, 1968-1986; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 103, Folder 10)
    - Air Express International Corporation, 1976-1985; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 103, Folder 11)
    - Al Golden, Incorporated, 1976; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 103, Folder 12)
    - Allstate Transportation Company, 1978-1980; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 103, Folder 13)
    - Alltemp Distribution Company, 1988; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 103, Folder 14)
    - American Freight Systems, Incorporated, 1988; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 103, Folder 15)
    - Applied Texture, Incorporated, 1979-1982; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 103, Folder 16)
    - Armour Food Company, 1979-1982; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 103, Folder 17)
    - Arrow Motor Freight, 1976; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 103, Folder 18)
    - Aslesens Company, 1979; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 103, Folder 19)
    - Associated Milk Producers, Incorporated, 1996-1997; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 103, Folder 20)
    - Atlas Plastics Corporation, 1983-1984; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 103, Folder 21)
    - August Dieke Transfer, 1979-1987; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 103, Folder 22)
    - Barber Transportation Company, 1970-1984; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 103, Folder 23)
    - Barrett Moving and Storage, 1985-1988; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 103, Folder 24)
    - Bay and Bay Transfer Company, 1983-1985; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - Beatrice Meats/Swift-Eckrich, 1985-1988; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - Bell Cold Storage Company, 1974-1988; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - Beltmann North American Company, 1976-1983; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - Ben Franklin Drivers, 1975-1984; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - Berger Transfer and Storage Company, 1983-1987; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - Bergold Properties, Incorporated, 1985; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - Bright Trucking, Incorporated, 1982-1984; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - Bryan Fisher, Incorporated, 1981; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - Bug Eye Transportation, 1981; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 104, Folder 10)
    - Burlington-Northern Air Freight, Incorporated, 1979-1981; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 104, Folder 11)
    - C.F.S. Continental, 1981-1982; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 104, Folder 12)
    - Campbell Soup Company, 1978-1995; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 104, Folder 13)
    - Capp Homes [1/2], 1974-1978; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 104, Folder 14)
    - Capp Homes [2/2], 1978-1980; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 104, Folder 15)
    - Carpenter Transfer, Incorporated, 1980-1981; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 104, Folder 16)
    - Century Mercury Motor Freight, Incorporated [1/2], 1975-1978; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 104, Folder 17)
    - Century Mercury Motor Freight, Incorporated [2/2], 1979-1990; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - Chicago Avenue Transfer, Incorporated, 1973-1983; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - Churchill Truck Lines, 1990; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - City of Worthington, 1979; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - Clark Transport Company, Incorporated, 1976-1978; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - Clear View Optical, Incorporated, 1984; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 105, Folder 6)
    - Commerce Freight Terminals, 1981-1985; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 105, Folder 7)
    - Consolidated Freightways, Incorporated, 1978-1986; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 105, Folder 8)
    - Continental Minnesota, Incorporated, 1976-1980; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 105, Folder 9)
    - Cotter and Company, 1976-1981; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 105, Folder 10)
    - County of Nobles, 1982-1986; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 105, Folder 11)
    - Crouse Cartage Company, 1978-1984; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 105, Folder 12)
    - Culligan Water Conditioning Company, 1977-1984; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 105, Folder 13)
    - Dairy Fresh Products, 1970-1971; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 105, Folder 14)
    - Dahlen Transport, 1969-1980; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 105, Folder 15)
    - Distron Division, Burger King Corporation, 1986-1987; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 105, Folder 16)
    - Driver Power, Incorporated, 1974-1988; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 105, Folder 17)
    - Drivers Service, Incorporated, 1984-1986; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 105, Folder 18)
    - E.S.B., Incorporated, 1970-1980; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 105, Folder 19)
    - Edson Express, Incorporated, 1986; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 105, Folder 20)
    - Emery Air Freight Corporation, 1976-1989; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 105, Folder 21)
    - Exide Company, 1988; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 105, Folder 22)
    - Express Cartage, 1989; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - Farmhand, Incorporated, 1978; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 2)
    - Fresh Pack, Incorporated, 1977; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 3)
    - Furnell and Webb Transfer Company, 1976-1977; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 4)
    - G.M.W., Incorporated, 1977-1980; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 5)
    - Gallagher Transfer, Incorporated, 1985; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 6)
    - Garrett Freight Lines, Incorporated, 1977; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 7)
    - Gateway Foods, 1981-1991; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 8)
    - General Sheet Metal Corporation, 1988; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 9)
    - Genuine Parts Company, 1985; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 10)
    - Gerdin Transfer, Incorporated, 1981; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 11)
    - Gibson Trucking Company, 1987; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 12)
    - Glendenning Motorways, Incorporated, 1978-1990; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 13)
    - Graebel Movers, B&E Packing Services, Incorporated, 1987; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 14)
    - Greif Brothers Corporation, 1977; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 15)
    - Gurley Nut, 1987; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 16)
    - H. Brooks and Company, 1978-1987; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 17)
    - Hankin Transportation, 1980; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 18)
    - Harrison House, 1979; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 19)
    - Hart Motor Express, Incorporated, 1978; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 20)
    - Heartland Food Company, 1991-1998; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 21)
    - Henry Lambert Trucking Company, 1976-1977; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 22)
    - Hugo Schultz, Incorporated, 1989; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 23)
    - Hyman Freightways, Incorporated [1/2], 1980-1982; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 24)
    - Hyman Freightways, Incorporated [2/2], 1986; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 25)
    - I. Bachall Steel and Supply, 1983; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 26)
    - J&J Transfer Company, 1986; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 27)
    - Jack Frost, Incorporated, 1976; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 28)
    - Janesville Auto Transport Company, 1980-1984; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 29)
    - John Sexton and Company, 1982; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 30)
    - KNUJ/KXLP, Incorporated, 1984; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 31)
    - Kato Movers and Storage Company, 2000; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 32)
    - Kenosha Auto Transport Company, 1979-1990; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - Key City Oil Company/Phillips Petroleum Company, 1970-1971; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 2)
    - LaBelle Storage and Moving Company, 1970-1984; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - Labor Services Company, 1981; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - Lake State Transport, Incorporated, 1980; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 5)
    - Landry Transfer, Incorporated, 1986; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 6)
    - Landy Packing Company, 1976-1980; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 7)
    - LaSalle Cartage Company, Incorporated, 1978-1983; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 8)
    - Larson Warehouse, 1975-1980; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 9)
    - Lindsay Brothers Company, 1982; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 10)
    - Loomis Courier Service, 1976; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 11)
    - Lundin Construction Company, 1984; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 12)
    - Luxton Truck Line, 1981-1988; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 13)
    - M.F. Bank and Company, 1984; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 14)
    - M&R Paving and Excavating, Incorporated, 1995-1996; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 15)
    - M.T.S. Company, 1980; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 16)
    - Mackay Envelope Company, 1979; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 17)
    - Maiers Transfer and Storage, 1974-1984; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 18)
    - Masonite Corporation, 1976-1990; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 19)
    - Mats, Incorporated, 1988; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 20)
    - May Company, 1976-1980; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 21)
    - McKesson Chemical Company, 1981; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 22)
    - Medical Oxygen and Equipment Company, 1987; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 23)
    - Metal-Matic, Incorporated, 1976-1981; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 24)
    - Metcalf Moving and Storage Company, 1978-1979; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 25)
    - Metz Baking Company, 1988-1992; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 26)
    - Midwest Driver Corporation, 1974-1981; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 27)
    - Midwest Machinery Movers, Incorporated, 1974-1977; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - Midwest Motor Transport, 1975; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - Midwest Wine Company, Incorporated, 1975; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - Milwaukee Motor Transportation Company, 1979-1980; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 108, Folder 4)
    - Minneapolis Van and Warehouse Company, 1979-1983; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - Minnesota Boxed Meat, 1987; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 108, Folder 6)
    - Minnesota Express, 1979-1987; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 108, Folder 7)
    - Minnesota-Wisconsin Truck Lines, Incorporated, 1979; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 108, Folder 8)
    - Mix Transfer Company, 1978-1980; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 108, Folder 9)
    - Mohawk Transfer and Storage Company, 1978-1979; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 108, Folder 10)
    - Murphy Delivery Service, Incorporated, 1978-1984; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 108, Folder 11)
    - Murphy Motor Freight Lines, Incorporated, 1965-1967; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 108, Folder 12)
    - Murphy Motor Freight, Shamrock Division, 1982-1984; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 108, Folder 13)
    - Murphy Rigging and Erecting, 1987-1990; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 108, Folder 14)
    - Murphy Warehouse Company, 1975-1985; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 108, Folder 15)
    - Musingwear, Incorporated, 1979; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 108, Folder 16)
    - National Drivers, Incorporated, 1974-1979; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 108, Folder 17)
    - National Food Stores, Incorporated, 1978-1979; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 108, Folder 18)
    - National Warehouses, Incorporated, 1978-1980; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 108, Folder 19)
    - Neptune World Wide Moving, Incorporated, 1974-1981; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 108, Folder 20)
    - Neuendorf Transportation Company, 1977-1980; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 108, Folder 21)
    - New Ulm Concrete Products, Incorporated, 1990-1995; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 108, Folder 22)
    - New Ulm Freight Lines, Incorporated, 1977-1981; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 108, Folder 23)
    - New Ulm Wholesale, Incorporated, 1987-1991; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 108, Folder 24)
    - Noel Transfer, 1974; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 108, Folder 25)
    - Norman G. Jensen, Incorporated, 1978; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 108, Folder 26)
    - North Star Concrete Company [1/2], 1987-1990; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - North Star Concrete Company [2/2], 1990-1995; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - Northern Cargo Association, 1980-1983; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - Northland Beverages, Incorporated, 1990; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - Northwest Produce Company, Incorporated, 1979-1980; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - Northwest Transfer and Warehouse, Incorporated, 1981-1985; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 109, Folder 6)
    - OCHS Brick and Tile Company, 1979-2005; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 109, Folder 7)
    - Oak Hills Living Center, Highland Manor [1/2], 1990-1996; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 109, Folder 8)
    - Oak Hills Living Center, Highland Manor [2/2], 1997-1998; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 109, Folder 9)
    - Pacific Gamble Robinson Company, 1979-1983; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 109, Folder 10)
    - Pacific Intermountain Express Company (P.I.E.) [1/2], 1979-1980; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 109, Folder 11)
    - Pacific Intermountain Express Company (P.I.E.) [2/2], 1980-1989; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 109, Folder 12)
    - Pennant Food Company (Van Den Bergh Foods Company), 1998; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 109, Folder 13)
    - Pepsi-Cola, 1989-1996; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 109, Folder 14)
    - Perkins Motor Transport Company, 1962-1964; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 109, Folder 15)
    - Perlman Roque Company (North), 1982; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - Pictsweet Frozen Foods, Incorporated, undated; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - Pillsbury Company, 1982-1984; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - Pratt's Express Company, 1974-1975; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 110, Folder 4)
    - Preferred Products, Incorporated, 1978-1979; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - Prepared Foods International, 1976-1979; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - Quality Drivers, 1987; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 110, Folder 7)
    - Quickie Transport Company, 1969-1978; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 110, Folder 8)
    - Quinn Transfer Company, 1978-1979; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 110, Folder 9)
    - Rapidways Truck Leasing, 1981; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 110, Folder 10)
    - Raymond Motor Transportation Company, Incorporated, 1975; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 110, Folder 11)
    - Red Owl Stores, Incorporated, 1976-1981; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 110, Folder 12)
    - Roadway Express, Incorporated, 1982-1990; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 110, Folder 13)
    - Rocket Transfer, 1981-1982; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 110, Folder 14)
    - Rosewood Corporation, 1981; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 110, Folder 15)
    - Royal Foods, 1985; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 110, Folder 16)
    - Ruan Transport, 1978; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 110, Folder 17)
    - S.J. Groves and Sons Company, 1974; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 110, Folder 18)
    - Salt Creek Freightways, 1984-1985; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 110, Folder 19)
    - Schwens Dairy, 1975; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 110, Folder 20)
    - Security Warehouse, 1974-1976; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 110, Folder 21)
    - Seeco, Incorporated, 1982; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 110, Folder 22)
    - Service Ideas, Incorporated, 1985; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 110, Folder 23)
    - Shari Candies, Incorporated [1/2], 1986-2000; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 110, Folder 24)
    - Shari Candies, Incorporated [2/2], 1990-2003; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 110, Folder 25)
    - Shulman Air Freight, 1978; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 110, Folder 26)
    - Silent Knight Security System, 1987; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 110, Folder 27)
    - Skellet Van and Storage Company, 1979; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 110, Folder 28)
    - Sky and Land Express, 1980-1981; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 110, Folder 29)
    - Smith's Transfer Corporation, 1975-1984; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 110, Folder 30)
    - Southern Minnesota Construction Company, 1998; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - Space Center Minnesota, Incorporated, 1975-1987; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - Spartech Plastics, 1991-1995; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 111, Folder 3)
    - State Distributing Company, Incorporated, 1994; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - Stemm Transfer and Storage Company, 1976-1986; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 111, Folder 5)
    - Sterling Cartage Company, 1974-1983; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 111, Folder 6)
    - Stinar Corporation, 1985; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 111, Folder 7)
    - Stokely-Van Camp, Incorporated [1/3], 1968-1982; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 111, Folder 8)
    - Stokely-Van Camp, Incorporated [2/3], 1970; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 111, Folder 9)
    - Stokely-Van Camp, Incorporated [3/3], 1970-1971; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 111, Folder 10)
    - Super Valu Stores, Incorporated, 1982-1989; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 111, Folder 11)
    - Superior Concrete Block Company, 1991; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 111, Folder 12)
    - Team Central Company, Incorporated, 1973-1984; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 111, Folder 13)
    - Terry Brothers, Incorporated, 1974-1979; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 111, Folder 14)
    - Tooltech, Incorporated, 1981; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 111, Folder 15)
    - Town and Country Foods, 1988; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 111, Folder 16)
    - Tracy Bottling Company, Incorporated, 1966-1971; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 112, Folder 1)
    - Transportation Systems, Incorporated, 1973-1974; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 112, Folder 2)
    - Troll Cartage Company, 1974; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 112, Folder 3)
    - Trucking, Incorporated, 1974-1985; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 112, Folder 4)
    - Twin City Freight, Incorporated, 1979; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 112, Folder 5)
    - Twin City Produce Supplies, 1987; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 112, Folder 6)
    - Tyson Truck Lines, 1987-1990; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 112, Folder 7)
    - United Foods, Incorporated [1/2], 1984-1987; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 112, Folder 8)
    - United Foods, Incorporated [2/2], 1990-1992; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 112, Folder 9)
    - United Foods, Incorporated/Stokely-Van Camp, Incorporated, 1969-1990; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 112, Folder 10)
    - United Van Bus Delivery [1/10], 1974-1976; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 112, Folder 11)
    - United Van Bus Delivery [2/10], 1977; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 112, Folder 12)
    - United Van Bus Delivery [3/10], 1977; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - United Van Bus Delivery [4/10], 1977; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 113, Folder 2)
    - United Van Bus Delivery [5/10], 1978; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 113, Folder 3)
    - United Van Bus Delivery [6/10], 1978-1979; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 113, Folder 4)
    - United Van Bus Delivery [7/10], 1979; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - United Van Bus Delivery [8/10], 1980; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 113, Folder 6)
    - United Van Bus Delivery [9/10], 1980; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 114, Folder 1)
    - United Van Bus Delivery [10/10], 1981-1987; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 114, Folder 2)
    - United Van Bus Delivery, Marathon Division, 1985-1988; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 114, Folder 3)
    - VanVoorst Trucking, Incorporated, 1985; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 114, Folder 4)
    - Volk Transfer, 1976-1977; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 114, Folder 5)
    - Wallner Construction Company, 1987-1993; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 114, Folder 6)
    - Ward Transfer, Incorporated, 1974; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 114, Folder 7)
    - Waymouth Farms, 1984; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 114, Folder 8)
    - Wholesale Produce Supply Company, 1977-1987; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 114, Folder 9)
    - Widholm Transfer Company, 1974-1980; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 114, Folder 10)
    - Winona Van Norman Division of Hein-Warner, 1981-1986; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 114, Folder 11)
    - Wintz Transportation Company, 1977-1982; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 114, Folder 12)
    - World Wide, Incorporated, 1979-1981; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 114, Folder 13)
    - Worthington Regional Hospital, 1978-1998; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 114, Folder 14)
    - Yellow Freight Systems, Incorporated, 1982-1990; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 114, Folder 15)
    - Zuccaro's Produce, 1982; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 114, Folder 16)
- Teamster Records, Series 4